save the trees more ePaper I know we do
더 많은 나무를 저장하십시오 ePaper 나는 우리가 알고있다.
have a question from no one
아무에게도 질문 이 없다.
oh yeah quotation that's their name from
오, 그래, 그들의 이름이 인용구
someone named no one that's right so no
아무도 그렇게 옳지 않은 사람
one wants to know and this is about the
하나는 알고 싶어하고 이것은 관한 것입니다
boogie board sink that we covered you a
우리가 덮여 부기 보드 싱크 당신
month ago
한달 전에
ish yeah I love that thing that's the
나는 그 것을 사랑한다 .
thing that you're using them yeah yeah
것은 당신이 그래를 사용하고 있는지
yes like a ePaper speaking of e paper he
예 전자 종이의 전자 종이의 말하기와 같은 그
paper tablet that saves via bluetooth or
블루투스 또는
USB connect yes to an app yes that's
USB를 통해 응용 프로그램에 연결 예
love it yeah so the question is does the
사랑해, 그래, 그 질문은
boogie board sync app work on Raspberry
라스베리에 부기 보드 동기화 응용 프로그램 작업
Pi so first off if you want to know what
당신이 무엇을 알고 싶은 경우에 Pi 그래서 먼저 떨어져.
we're talking about go to cat v dot TV /
우리는 고양이 V 도트 TV에 이동에 대해 얘기하고 /
e paper so we covered this device about
전자 종이 그래서 우리는 이 장치에 대해 다뤘다.
a month ago and it came as a result of
한 달 전, 그 결과로
you guys looking at some a paper a
너희들 종이 좀 보면서.
couple weeks prior yeah love it right
몇주 전 예 맞아.
but my question was does it save and can
하지만 내 질문 은 그것을 저장 하고 할 수 있습니다
i sync it up no don't make such a thing
나는 그것을 동기화 하지 않는다. 그런 일을 하지 마라.
Jeff in the next week he's like I bought
제프 는 다음 주에 내가 산 것 같아.
this school and I need it I think it's
이 학교와 나는 그것이 필요 하다고 생각해.
amazing so I've been using this
놀랍 도록 나는 이것을 사용 해왔다.
consistently away when I use it for when
지속적으로 멀리 나는 경우에 사용할 때
I'm doing negotiations I'm using it for
나는 그것을 위해 사용하고있는 협상을하고 있다.
meetings like all the time I'm using it
내가 사용하고있는 모든 시간과 같은 회의
I would love it just you know not to
나는 네가 좋아하지 않는 것을 좋아할 것이다.
digress or anything or sidestep but for
탈선 또는 무엇인가 또는 옆 걸음
the kids to draw on and do sherwin stuff
무서워 하고 쉐윈 물건을 할 애들.
like that because they can save it wipe
그들이 그것을 지울 수 있기 때문에 그렇게 닦아 라.
it wipe it yep there's no paper they get
그것은 닦아내 는데 그들이 얻은 종이가 없다.
stacks of paper mom and dad you know
당신이 아는 종이 엄마와 아빠의 스택
what I'm talking about and then you got
그 다음 내가 이야기하고 당신이있어
to go through and recycle it and it's
가고 그것을 재활용하고 그것을
heartbreaking to do so but you've got to
그렇게하기에는 가슴이 아팠지만
do it you got to do it without the kids
애들없이해라.
knowing so it's like 11 o'clock at night
밤 11시와 같아서 알기.
and yes sorry kids so the reason I
그리고 미안 아이. 그렇기 때문에 나는
wanted was to be able to sit like to
같이 앉아 있을 수 있었으면 좋겠다.
save my notes and sync them up and you
내 노트를 저장하고 그들을 동기화하고
know compile them so I'll use like PDF
PDF를 사용하도록 컴파일을 아십시오.
and all because they're all safe I'll
그리고 그들은 모두 안전 하기 때문에 나는 모두거야.
put them all into one file exactly yeah
정확히 모두 하나의 파일에 넣으십시오.
so it's wonderful that way so this
그래서 지금이 그런 식으로 훌륭합니다
question relates to how it syncs up and
질문은 동기화하는 방법과 관련이 있습니다.
how you get those files and so the
어떻게 그 파일들을 얻고 그래서
question doesn't work with Raspberry Pi
질문 은 Raspberry Pi와 함께 작동하지 않습니다.
the show
쇼
is yes what it does No so I haven't know
예, 그렇습니다. 아니오, 모릅니다.
I personally have not synced it up to
나는 개인적으로 그것을 동기화하지 않았다.
the Raspberry Pi but on the website my
라스베리 파이 하지만 웹 사이트에 내
boogie board comm say for the sink nine
부기 보드 통신은 싱크대 9에 대한
point seven it says which computer
포인트 7 그것은 어떤 컴퓨터
operating systems are compatible with
운영 체제는 다음과 호환 됩니다.
the boogie board sink the boogie board
부기 보드 침몰 부기 보드
sink is compatible with any operating
싱크는 모든 작동 과 호환 가능합니다.
system that recognizes a USB storage
USB 저장 장치를 인식하는 시스템
device the VVC software is compatible
장치는 VVC 소프트웨어 호환
with Mac OS X 10.8 and I solve oh wait
맥 OS X 10.8과 나는 오 기다려 해결
the X stands for 10 yeah but so s X 10.8
X는 10을 의미 하지만 X는 10.8입니다.
I'm just I'm reading over OS x yeah hey
난 그냥 내가 봐 그래 OS X를 통해 읽고 있어요 있어요
yes
예
Windows Vista 7 and 8 and then they're
윈도우 비스타 7과 8 그리고 그들은
saying if you're using Windows 10 please
Windows 10을 사용하고 있다면
contact support now doesn't mention
연락처 지원은 이제 언급하지 않습니다.
Linux there but it does so it shows up
거기에 리눅스가 있지만 그것이 나타나기 때문에
as a mass storage device when you plug
플러그 할 때 대용량 저장 장치로 사용
it in you have file system access to the
파일 시스템에 액세스 할 수 있습니다.
PDF yes that's correct
PDF 네, 맞습니다.
brilliant yeah now the one feature that
이제는 하나의 특징 인 화려한 예
will not work with the Raspberry Pi you
라즈베리 파이 당신과 함께 작동하지 않습니다
tell is remember how I showed you
내가 너 에게 보여준 것을 기억하라.
there's a button on the little pen
작은 펜에 버튼 이있다.
yeah so with that button you can use
예 , 버튼을 사용하면
your boogie board sync to do like live
귀하의 부기 보드 동기화 라이브처럼 할
lives on like a PowerPoint projector up
파워 포인트 프로젝터 처럼 살아요.
on a screen so that will not work with
화면에 그래서이 작동하지 않습니다
the Raspberry Pi but as far as being
까지 인 것으로하지만, 라즈베리 파이
able to sync it and transfer your files
그것을 동기화하고 파일을 전송할 수 있습니다.
absolutely it will work so you can blue
절대적으로 작동 하므로 파란색으로 표시 할 수 있습니다.
through the device you can email them
기기를 통해 이메일로 보낼 수 있습니다.
then to yourself or you could just use
그때 너 자신에게 또는 너는 다만 사용할 수 있었다
the cable connected via USB so there you
그래서이 USB를 통해 연결된 케이블 당신
go no one who's actually someone it does
실제로 누군가있는 사람이 없다.
work on the Raspberry Pi ok and to take
라스베리 파이 파이 에서 일하고 받아 들인다.
that one step further there are actual
그 한 걸음 더 나아가 실제
projects in development third-party
개발 타사 프로젝트
projects that allow the boogie board
부기 보드를 허용하는 프로젝트
sync to communicate with Linux because
Linux와 통신하려면 동기화하십시오.
remember the Raspberry Pi is Linux at it
라즈베리 파이는 그것을 리눅스 기억
right right right so the Raspberry Pi 3
맞아, 오른쪽 라즈베리 파이 3
for example has built-in bluetooth and
예 를 들어 내장 된 블루투스 및
it has 4 USB to ports right so you can
포트 당 4 개의 USB 포트가있어
connect it by USB or you can connect it
USB로 연결 하거나 연결할 수 있습니다.
by bluetooth but because the app is not
블루투스로 하지만 앱이 아니기 때문에
natively supported what can you possibly
네이티브 지원
do other than as you say accessing it as
네가 말한 것 이외의 다른 방법으로
an external hard drive kind of setup
외부 하드 드라이브 종류의 설정
right but check this out so if you do a
맞았지 만 이것을 확인해보십시오 .
quick search on Google for boogie-board
부기 보드 에 대한 Google의 빠른 검색
sync Linux because remember Raspberry Pi
Raspberry Pi를 기억하기 때문에 Linux를 동기화하십시오.
is powered by Linux you're gonna install
설치할 Linux에서 제공됩니다.
like raspbian first one that comes up is
올라 오는 raspbian 첫번째 것 같이 이다
called boogie sync tablet introduction
부기 동기화 타블렛 소개
this is an implementation of the user
이것은 사용자의 구현
space driver for using the boogie board
부기 보드를 사용하기위한 공간 드라이버
sync as a
~ 같이 동기화 하다
tablet under Linux blows away your
리눅스에서 태블릿 멀리 불면 당신의
lottery that some of the features
복권의 일부 기능
doesn't work carrying on it says there
거기에 계속해서 작동하지 않는다고 말한다.
are two apps one is for USB input and
하나는 USB 입력 용이고
one for Bluetooth that's awesome it uses
이 사용 끝내 블루투스 하나
PI USB Pi Blues to interface with the
PI USB 파이 블루스와 인터페이스
device and the you input system via the
장치 및 귀하 입력 시스템
EU dev for Python I love it so it
파이썬에 대한 EU dev에 나는 그래서 그것을 사랑
generates input signals directly over
직접 입력 신호를 생성 합니다.
that connection and it warns that it is
그 연결 은 그것이라고 경고한다.
still in the early days however it is
아직도이다 그러나 초기에
operational and it's available that's
운영 가능 하며 사용 가능 합니다.
the first Google result for what was my
내 첫 번째 Google 검색 결과
search what was your search boogie-board
귀하의 검색 부기 보드 검색
sync linux x so we know that you know
Linux x를 동기화하면 알 수 있습니다.
these are it's on github it's an open
이들은 그것이 개방의 GitHub의에의있다
source project there are other projects
소스 프로젝트에 다른 프로젝트가있다.
as well there's one called mobile read
뿐만 아니라 모바일 읽기라는 것이 있습니다.
for boogie board there's sync for boogie
부기 보드 용 부기 용 동기화
board
판
I'm just looking through the the results
나는 그 결과를 보고있다.
here on Google whatever search engine
여기에 Google 검색 엔진
you're using so that's one for you
너는 그렇게 사용하고있어.
anyway so good to know that that's the
어쨌든 그걸 알면 좋겠다 .
nature of open source and how things get
오픈 소스의 본질과 그 것들이 얻는 방법
work there you go
거기에서 일 하자.
and it's pretty cheap on Amazon it's a
아마존 에서 꽤 싸다 .
waste to end up something I own like I I
내가 좋아하는 무언가를 끝내기위한 낭비
can't like I think we all need one of it
우리 모두가 그 중 하나가 필요하다고 생각하는 것 같지 않아.
I can't stop thinking about it so it
나는 그것에 대해 그 때문에 생각을 멈출 수 없다
said well the you're not really
너 진짜로 아니야.
replacing the paper yes we are legit you
종이 교체 우리 는 합법적입니다.
are about it if we if all three of us
우리 셋 모두가
have this boogie board sync hundreds of
이 부기 보드와 수백 개의 동기화
dollars cheaper than a tablet yeah like
같은 그래 태블릿보다 저렴 달러
a say an iPad or like a Samsung Galaxy
iPad를 말하는거나 삼성 갤럭시 처럼
Tab or something like that and do away
탭이나 뭐 그런 식으로 멀리하지 마라.
with this every week yeah well see
이 매주 네, 잘 보입니다.
here's what I love about it so when I'm
내가 사랑할 때 그걸 좋아해.
doing negotiations for contracts a lot
계약에 대한 협상 을 많이하고있다.
of our proposals are back and forth
우리 제안서가 앞뒤로
digitally so that you know when you've
디지털 방식으로
got an entire page of language instead I
대신 전체 언어 페이지가 있어요.
have it - like retype it yeah somebody
그것을 가지고 - 그것을 다시 입력 좋아, 누군가
can you know you take the digital file
당신은 당신이 디지털 파일 을 가지고 있다는 것을 알 수 있습니까?
you make your edits and you send it back
너는 너의 편집을하고 너는 그것을 다시 보낸다.
yes so I can bargain digitally that way
예, 그렇게하면 디지털 방식으로 거래 할 수 있습니다.
even though we're in the room so with my
우리가 방에 있어도 내
notes I actually don't have to have a
메모 실제로 나는 필요가 없습니다.
binder or any paper with me anymore it's
바인더 나 다른 종이를 더 이상 가지고 있지 않습니다.
amazing and it's so much so that I've
놀랍습니다. 너무 많이 있어
been at the table and I've been stopped
테이블에 있었고 나는 멈췄다.
in the middle of a presentation as I was
프레젠테이션 중간 에 내가 했던 것처럼
going what is that
그게 뭐니?
yeah and I explained it to them I show
그래 나는 내가 보여 그들에게 그것을 설명
them he show you and I go here and I
그 사람이 너를 보여주고 내가 여기와 나는 간다.
draw a smiley face i sink it I email it
웃는 얼굴을 그 립니다 . 나는 그것을 가라 앉힌다. 나는 그것을 이메일로 보낸다.
to them they pull up the phone there's a
그들에게 전화를 걸어
PDF of the smiley face and they're like
웃는 얼굴의 PDF 그들은 같은거야
I need that and I go let me get you the
나는 그것을 필요로 하고 내가 너를 얻도록 내버려 둔다.
link so if I've got DV / E paper right
DV / E 종이가 맞다 면 링크 해주세요.
that's right yes so people have been
그 바로 네 그래서 사람들이왔다입니다
buying it just simply by seeing me use
그냥 나를보고 사용하여 구입
it it's our best thing I've ever seen
그것은 내가 본 것 우리의 가장 좋은 방법입니다
it's really cool but I thought the best
정말 근사 하긴하지만 최고라고 생각 했어.
thing I've ever seen but I do like
내가 본 것 중에 내가 좋아하는 것
Dustin I do like it a lot that's the
Dustin 나는 그것을 많이 좋아한다.
biggie books coming soon to Linux
리눅스에 곧 출시 될 큰 책
[Music]
[음악]
[Applause]
[박수 갈채]